<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Menus on Magdalena Łucka</title>
    <link>https://magdalucka.github.io/en/menu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Menus on Magdalena Łucka</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://magdalucka.github.io/en/menu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Articles</title>
      <link>https://magdalucka.github.io/en/menu/articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://magdalucka.github.io/en/menu/articles/</guid>
      <description>List of articles 2025 Title: Investigation of machine learning algorithms to determine glaciers displacements
Authors: Łucka Magdalena
Journal: Remote Sensing Applications: Society and Environment
DOI: 10.1016/j.rsase.2025.101476
Full-text: click hereto read 2024 Title: Impact of mining-induced seismicity on land subsidence occurrence
Authors: Witkowski Wojciech, Łucka Magdalena, Guzy Artur, Sudhaus Henriette, Barańska Anna, Hejmanowski Ryszard
Journal: Remote Sensing of Environment
DOI: 10.1016/j.rse.2023.113934
Full-text: click hereto read 2023 Title: Temporal development of the displacement field of the Ponzano landslide in February 2017</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://magdalucka.github.io/en/menu/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://magdalucka.github.io/en/menu/contact/</guid>
      <description>e-mail: magdalena.lucka@agh.edu.plResearchGateLinkedInGoogle ScholarAGH BaDAP</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other activities</title>
      <link>https://magdalucka.github.io/en/menu/other/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://magdalucka.github.io/en/menu/other/</guid>
      <description>Conferences 2024 XXIV Conference of PhD Students and Young Scientists
Place: Wroclaw, Poland
Date: 23-25 October, 2024
Presented topic:
Revealing changes in displacement pattern of the rapid landslide with highresolution European Polar Science Week
Place: Copenhagen, Denmark
Date: 03-06 September, 2024
Presented topic:
Determination of glaciers’ movements based on a machine learning approach EGU General Assembly
Place: Vienna, Austria
Date: 14-19 April, 2024
Presented topic:
Potential of employing a machine learning model for glacier motion monitoring XXXIII Szkoła Ekspolatacji Podziemnej</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://magdalucka.github.io/en/menu/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://magdalucka.github.io/en/menu/projects/</guid>
      <description>Novel view on the study of glacier kinematics in the context of global climate change Role: principal investigator
Duration: 02/2023 - 02/2026
Source of funding: National Scientific Centre of Poland
Main goals: The project aims to develop a new method for monitoring glacier movements using SAR data and machine learning. By combining the Offset-Tracking (OT) and DInSAR technique, with high-resolution SAR images, it will analyze changes in glacier kinematics, detect anomalies, and assess speed trends in Greenland and Svalbard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRELUDIUM 21</title>
      <link>https://magdalucka.github.io/en/menu/preludium/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://magdalucka.github.io/en/menu/preludium/</guid>
      <description>Novel view on the study of glacier kinematics in the context of global climate change
Goal and siginifcance The project aims to develop a new method for monitoring glacier movements using SAR data and machine learning. By combining the Offset-Tracking (OT) and DInSAR technique, with high-resolution SAR images, it will analyze changes in glacier kinematics, detect anomalies, and assess speed trends in Greenland and Svalbard. The research involves testing machine learning algorithms to optimize displacement assessment, followed by comparative analyses using GIS software.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
